(Sheldon:)Two one six four two zero
(Sheldon:)one nine eight nine.
(Sheldon:)And that, little lady,
is pi to a thousand places.
(Amy:)I'd say I'm sorry I asked,
(Amy:)except I didn't.
(Sheldon:)Oh, look, it's the
Scientific American
(Sheldon:)that covered the paper
Leonard and I wrote.
(Amy:)Oh, let me see.
(Sheldon:)I have mixed feelings
about doing interviews.
(Sheldon:)I like the part where I talk.
(Sheldon:)I do not like the part
where the other man talks.
(Amy:)Sheldon, this article doesn't
mention Leonard at all.
(Sheldon:)Well, that
can't be right.
(Amy:)It only refers to
"Dr. Cooper and his team."
(Amy:)Did you even talk about him?
(Sheldon:)All I did was answer a few
questions about the theory.
(Sheldon:)And then expressed my gratitude
that Scientific American
(Sheldon:)doesn't include any of those
smelly perfume cards.
(Amy:)Poor Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Why? The theory
he came up with
(Sheldon:)just got mentioned in
Scientific American.
(Sheldon:)He ought to be thrilled.
(Amy:)He might not be.
(Sheldon:)Oh, maybe you're right.
(Sheldon:)He is kind of a lump.
(Amy:)Think about it.
(Amy:)How would you feel
if you were referred to
(Amy:)as part of Leonard's team?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I'd be incensed.
(Amy:)So you see what
I'm getting at?
(Sheldon:)Squeaky wheel
gets the grease?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)Grass is always greener?
(Amy:)Try again.
(Sheldon:)Well, I don't know--
we're all Groot?
(Sheldon:)Just tell me.
(Amy:)Leonard is as much
a part of this paper
(Amy:)as you are,
and he was overlooked.
(Amy:)He's going to feel bad.
(Sheldon:)But it wasn't my fault.
(Sheldon:)I didn't exclude him.
(Sheldon:)And I didn't write the article.
(Amy:)Remember that time you didn't
get picked to pull the sword out
(Amy:)of the stone at Disneyland and
they let that other kid do it?
Oh, that kid!
(Amy:)Poor Leonard.
(Amy:)Exactly.
(Sheldon:)For the record,
that kid was a terrible choice.
(Sheldon:)If you cry when you drop
your churro,
(Sheldon:)you do not have what it takes
to rule England.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪